[{
        "question": "غوجو",
        "response": "غوجو"
    },
    {
        "question": "غيتو",
        "response": "غيتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "نوبارا",
        "response": "نوبارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "يامي",
        "response": "يامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "توجي",
        "response": "توجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوجي",
        "response": "يوجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايتادوري",
        "response": "ايتادوري"
    },
    {
        "question": "سوكونا",
        "response": "سوكونا"
    },
    {
        "question": "باندا",
        "response": "باندا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميغومي",
        "response": "ميغومي"
    },
    {
        "question": "شوسو",
        "response": "شوسو"
    },
    {
        "question": "غابي",
        "response": "غابي"
    },
    {
        "question": "استا",
        "response": "استا"
    },
    {
        "question": "نويل",
        "response": "نويل"
    },
    {
        "question": "يونو",
        "response": "يونو"
    },
    {
        "question": "غوجو عمكم",
        "response": "غوجو عمكم"
    },
    {
        "question": "يونا",
        "response": "يونا"
    },
    {
        "question": "يومير",
        "response": "يومير"
    },
    {
        "question": "ياغامي",
        "response": "ياغامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "لايت",
        "response": "لايت"
    },
    {
        "question": "بوروتو",
        "response": "بوروتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ناروتو",
        "response": "ناروتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايتاتشي",
        "response": "ايتاتشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "مادارا",
        "response": "مادارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوتشيها",
        "response": "اوتشيها"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوميكو",
        "response": "يوميكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيزوكو",
        "response": "نيزوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "سايتاما",
        "response": "سايتاما"
    },
    {
        "question": "اينوسكي",
        "response": "اينوسكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "تانجيرو",
        "response": "تانجيرو"
    },
    {
        "question": "لوفي",
        "response": "لوفي"
    },
    {
        "question": "زورو",
        "response": "زورو"
    },
    {
        "question": "اكازا",
        "response": "اكازا"
    },
    {
        "question": "باغي",
        "response": "باغي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميهوك",
        "response": "ميهوك"
    },
    {
        "question": "روجر",
        "response": "روجر"
    },
    {
        "question": "نامي",
        "response": "نامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "نانامي",
        "response": "نانامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيناتا",
        "response": "هيناتا"
    },
    {
        "question": "روبين",
        "response": "روبين"
    },
    {
        "question": "باكي",
        "response": "باكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "زيكو",
        "response": "زيكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كروكودايل",
        "response": "كروكودايل"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوياجي",
        "response": "اوياجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "رايلي",
        "response": "رايلي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايرين",
        "response": "ايرين"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميكاسا",
        "response": "ميكاسا"
    },
    {
        "question": "الوكا",
        "response": "الوكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هانجي",
        "response": "هانجي"
    },
    {
       "question": "زيرو تو",
        "response": "زيرو تو"
    },
    {
       "question": "مي مي",
        "response": "مي مي"
    },
    {
       "question": "نويل",
        "response": "نويل"
    },
    {
       "question": "شوكو",
        "response": "شوكو"
    },
    {
       "question": "ميوا",
       "response": "ميوا"
}]
